gemnation.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy at Gemnation

At Gemnation, we strive to better serve our customers. We also recognize that your privacy is important. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use Gemnation's website, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. 

### Data Collection

Gemnation collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit our website. This log information includes your browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

When purchasing, we require that you enter some personal information, including your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We may also request your credit card or other payment information depending on your payment preferences. For credit card purchases, this information is sent to your credit card issuing authority for verification and authorization. 

### Cookies

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service to you. Gemnation does this by storing your "Watch List" choices and your "Shopping Cart" in cookies. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, the above mentioned Gemnation features will not function properly without cookies. 

Gemnation and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website and to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. 

### Google Analytics

We use a tool called "Google Analytics" to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. We may you use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

In addition to the above we at times use the following Google services: Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show you ads on sites across the Internet. 

### Information Sharing

We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances: 

We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Gemnation, its users or the public.

If you purchase from us, we may share the purchase information that you submitted among all of our services (including in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Gemnation Corporation., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share aggregated information with others. Examples of this include the number of customers who purchased watches or how many users clicked on a particular page. 

### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

### Links

Gemnation may provide links to other third-party websites which are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these websites. 

### Changes to This Policy

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view.

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at [privacy@gemnation.com](mailto:privacy@gemnation.com).
